CONTACT

+966541798323

mailto:geesuth@outlook.com

https://geesuth.net/

Saudi Arabia Ishbilia, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

Workflows

https://github.com/GeeSuth https://github.com/gps-GeeSuth

SOCIAL

n Abdllah Bin Hatheem Ali

YOUTUBE CHANNEL

From 2012-Now
I was working in my channel
I got more than 130K views
And a lot of subscripes

QIWI Bank

In 2017 i was able to discover a high bug in qiwi.com And i was to get takeover for all servers and his reward me

Abdllah Aidross M Saleh

. Net Programmer & Security res-searcher

PERSONAL STATEMENT (REFRESH INFO)

10+ years' experience in the Programming and IT Industry, Strong knowledge of ASP.NET, C#, MVC framework ASP.NET Web Forms

Windows Application development

Experience in Web services (Web API) development

Experience in HTML5, jQuery, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap and AJAX Strong understanding of object-oriented programming

SOLID Principles Good analysis skills for troubleshooting Production issues.

Experience in popular web application frameworks

Database development (SQL Server & PL/SQL)

I have solid experience and understanding of systems development life cycle as well as being a Senior .Net Programmer

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Aden University, Lewder college (not a graduate)

2012 - 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior .Net at Fleet System

2020-Now

Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

- GPS
- PROTCOLS
- TCP, UDP
- C#
- Service Worker
- PHP
- Blazor
- Asynchronous

ITEC C# programmer

2019-2020

Madinah Road, Jeddah

- Net framework
- ASP
- Oracle DB

IT Department Manager:

2015-2019

Third industrial Jeddah, Saudi Arabia Reemas kids CO,

Computer Engineer (Sky Center)

2011-2015

Aden, Yemen

Internet Manager

2009-2001

Abyan, Yemen

- Visual Basic 6.0 Language.
- Started with SQL server (Query)



Hall of Fame of MICROSOFT

In March 2016 I got the Thanks from Microsoft Go to Microsoft

And search for GeeSuth

Hall of Fame of Sony

In the same year I was able to found bug in sony.com

SKILLS

- → Used the Programming in every thing
- → Analyst Data
- → Linux OS
- → Android
- → Windows All Version
- \rightarrow Internet
- → Data structure
- → Register
- \rightarrow API
- \rightarrow Re-searcher bugs.

MEMBERSHIPS

- StackOverFlow
- C# Corner
- Reddit
- <u>HackerOne</u>

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Reading
- Listening to music
- Walking
- Watch Films

Every day in my life ALhumLLah A got something New to my Experience:

♣ Android:

- → Xamarin | Ionic | Firebase | flutter
 - o Firebase Database of google
 - o Mega Servers (upload Files)
 - o SQLite
 - o A lot of Library

♣ ASPX:

- \rightarrow C# Web forms:
 - Telerik reports
 - o Ajax
 - o jQuery
 - Bootstrap
 - o Else.

♣ Security And pen tester:

- → Vulnerabilities:
 - o SQL Injection
 - o XSS (cross-site scripting)
 - Privilege Security
 - Uploading
 - o Run-time error
 - HackerOne Member
 - Exploit venerable servers
 - For all types

♣ Others:

- → Finger Machine | CCTV
 - Employers Management (fingers)
 - o Install CCTV Camera

In IT department I Learn and do a lot of things:

- Repair and care Server's
- Programming tools and systems by C#
- Developing tools for help others department in work
- Data integrity & care security issues
- Data Analyses processor
- Helpdesk others points PC and take care of

Programming:

- C#
 - .NET 6
 - .NET 5
 - Blazor
 - .Net Framework
 - Core 3
 - MVC 5
 - Web Form
 - Windows Application
 - ADO
 - ASP
 - Razor
 - API
 - Windows services
 - Entity framework
 - Entity Framework Core
 - OOP
 - Azure cloud
- Vb.Net
- Dart
- PHP
- C++

Smart phone platform:

- Xamarin
- Flutter
- Ionic

Databases:

- Oracle Database
- MS SQL server
- SQLite
- PhpMyAdmin
- Firebase database

Environment:

- Visual Studio
- VS Code
- Sublime
- Notepad++

OS:

- Windows
- Linux

Projects I worked on (follow link for more)

Just I finish many projects with most platforms some of was when I'm student and others like freelancer and Sure, some when I'm working for

Fleet System Co: t4gps.cloud

Saudi Arabia, Riyadh,

 Vehicle Tracking System (Web App & Windows App)

Short story: "This one of application I developing And I so proud of finishing this for fleet system, the idea of this system is to tracking vehicles and freezer machine, the windows part for management protocols and listening port of server, web app for controls vehicles and management and views on map, events, sensors and others features"

Techniques:

C#, Protocols, PHP 7, Listing, TCP, UDP, Geo, MariaDB, Devices of tracking, Teltonika, SMS Getaway's,

- Development Vehicle Tracking System (Integration with The Ministry of Transportation)

Short story: "According Ministry of Transport, All provider tracking system company need to Integration with WASL service for tracking vehicles and weight and speed"

Techniques:

PHP, API, Async, working with ELM company

Albiani Co:

Saudi Arabia, Riyadh,

- Gramoli (Ecosystem)

Short story: "ecosystem for new healthy restaurant in Riyadh for management subscribes and orders and offers and control all part in market app, Dashboard for administrator and layout for customers also employer permissions"

Techniques:

.Net 5, Blazor, Razor, API, Json web token, Authorization, Authentications, MudBlazor,, MS SQL, Entity framework, Interface, Service, DI,

GeeSuthSoft: geesuthsoft.net

Saudi Arabia, Riyadh,

- ERP (Multi-Platform)

Short story: "This app was resolving a lot of problems for companies, because this was working for Master Database, and serve clouding and user can open has system from anywhere"

Techniques:

.Net 5, C#, Blazer, MS SQL, ORM, Entity Framework, Reports, Sessions, localStorge, Authorization, Authentication, MudBlazor, JWT, SMS, API, API, UI Web Assembly

Hadramout Restaurant:

Saudi Arabia, Al-Riyadh

- ERP & POS System: (Windows App & Android App)

Short story: "I had strong experience with Accountant and how ERP system work so I did not hesitate to do that for customer, it's was a good opportunity, the problem here was the customer need application for android linked together with the same db for ERP to view reports for store balance and sales also purchase and customer want add 'Qud' from his phone "

Techniques:

C#, My DataAccerLayer, Telerik Report, Networks, Firebase database, Android studio, MS SQL server,

The Ministry of Education:

Yemen, Abyan

- Student Manager: (Web App & Windows App)

Short story: "after a war in Yemen, Legitimate government was wanting systems to student management, this app was help schools to linked with ministry together and a public for student to follow degree"

Techniques:

C#, ADO, Telerik Report, MVC, GPS, MS SQL Server

- View Models Images: (Windows App)

Short story: "This Application was help Mangers and supervisor

And Stores Employer for Add And searching Models Image for any models"

Techniques:

VB.Net, Access database, ADO, Networking, Async

Development View Models Images: (Android App)

Short story: "The same thing do but here work Online and from Android system too and linked together with before one, Add models from phone"

Techniques:

C#, Firebase database, ADO, Networking, Async, Xamarin, Camera process, Barcode reader

- Recycling Items Systems: (Windows App)

Short story: "the company I was work with has more than 35 branch and more than on country, our management was need so system can control sending and receiving items between branch and saving data to db and link to db for account system was used"

Techniques:

C#, MS SQL Server, VPN, Networks, Telerik Reports, threading data structure

- Live Attendance: (Windows App and Android)

Short story: "we was has maybe more than 70 employer in our company our boss was need to see liver attendance for employer when employ put finger in finger machine the same time we receiver notice in out office and records that in our db for attendance "

Techniques:

C#, MS SQL Server, VPN, Networks, Telerik Reports, threading data structure,

Xamarin, SDK (fingertic), Async,

Alert Document Expiration: (Windows App and Web App)

Short story: "like any company has employment contract and others document with finish date"

Techniques:

C#, MS SQL Server, Aspx, Ionic, entity framework, Um alQora

Short story: "top center has a lot of branches and this help employs to send problem and task to office for alert him is their problem all chatting and replay for

Task Management: (Web Application)

employ for more info or fixing replay"

Techniques:

TOP CENTER Co:

C#, ADO, Telerik Report, MVC

Alkema Co:

Saudi Arabia, Taif

- POS (point of Sales) : (Windows App)

Short story: "point of sales linked to others db" Techniques:

C#, ADO, Telerik Report

Sky Net Café:

Yemen, Abyan, Moudiah

- Internet Café Manager: (Windows App)

Short story: "internet café manager, help own café to calculate and open/close client device from server and monitor and control of others device in same networks also control internet (block sites)"

Techniques:

C#, ADO, Telerik Report, DevExpress, Networks, Ports, Access Database

Al-Stin Center:

Saudi Arabia, Jeddah, Al-stin Road

- Small ERP System: (Windows App)

Short story: "small enterprise resource planning for small corporation in Jeddah, Auto parts business in alstin road and point of sales and services cars doing for customers"

Techniques:

C#, My DataAccerLayer, Telerik Report, Networks,

ITIC Co:

Saudi Arabia, Jeddah, Madinah Road

ERP system: (Windows App)

Short story: "a big Enterprise resource planning" Techniques:

C#, Oracle Database, Entity Framework, MVC Strategy, Networks,